Can AI protect you from hackers? In this
video, I'll show you free AI agents for
cyber security that you must have. And
that's because the amount of AI powered
cyber attacks is on the rise. This year
alone, over 166 million individuals were
affected by cyber attacks. But it only
gets worse because AI powered attacks
have a four time higher success rate
than traditional fishing. For example,
new techniques like AI voice spoofing
where people can clone your voice and
call your bank, call your relatives and
extract money are becoming everyday
occurrence. And the truth is most people
have no idea how to guard against these.
Also, let's be honest, for a lot of us,
our digital life is slowly becoming more
important than our physical one. Now, we
all understand the importance of cyber
security, but the truth is most people
don't do anything about it. And that's
why I put together an AI first cyber
security course for 2026. I'll show you
the free AI agents that manage my own
cyber security and how to set them up.
And the best part is you only set them
up once and they run forever acting as
your digital bodyguards in a sense. Now,
just by having these free AI agents,
you'll already be ahead of 99% of people
when it comes to the cyber security. And
no, you don't have to be a professional
programmer to set these up. Now, the
first thing you have to understand about
cyber security is that most hacks and
breaches are not some crazy hacker
targeting you or some new zero day
attack. It's the stupidest things,
right? Such as social engineering,
someone pretending to be you and calling
your bank or just simple fishing links
that you accidentally click. Now, this
is actually good news because in order
to protect yourself against most hacks,
like 95% of cyber attacks, you don't
need to be a cyber security
professional. You just need to follow a
few basic things which we will cover in
this video. So pay attention. Number
one, setting up authenticator apps and
not SMS. SMS is not safe. A lot of you
are using SMS for two-factor
authentication. But what you don't
realize is that people can spoof your
SIM card and steal your two F8 codes
relatively easily. So instead of SMS,
you should use a proper authenticator
app like Google off one password off.
Doesn't matter. Use a proper off app,
not SMS. This already makes it much more
difficult to break into any accounts
rather than just having a single
password or password and SMS. Lesson
number two is to protect yourself
against fishing. Now fishing is usually
fake emails or messaging pretending to
be from companies that you trust. Your
bank, Amazon, Microsoft to steal
passwords or install malware. Now
actually the way to protect against
fishing is super simple and it's a
3-second thing. So anytime you see a
link that is suspicious or something
that's hyperl, just hover over it. Do
not click right away. Hover your mouse
over it and look in the bottom left of
your screen to see the actual redirect
URL. This will allow you to see where
the link actually wants to take you. And
if you think fishing attacks are a thing
of the past, think again because just
last week there was a huge fishing wave
hitting Pi Pi maintainers. And these are
actually professional developers. So
these are not dummies. These guys are
serious programmers and they were still
compromised. What happened is that the
hackers were emailing the developers and
maintainers of this Python package with
fake verify your email or account
suspended messages. So if anything has
some kind of urgency like quickly change
your password or your account is about
to be disabled, pay attention because
it's most likely a scam. If you see a
link and you are not sure if it's good
or not, just paste it into Vid Total
before clicking it. So, if you don't
know what V total is, it's a free
website that allows you to analyze
files, URLs, or just search to see if
something is malicious or if it's legit.
But let's be honest, pasting every
single link that you see into V total is
a lot of manual work. And you still
might sometimes miss it and click it on
accident. Which is why I built an AI
agent for this to automate the fishing
analysis of every single email that hits
your inbox. And the real beauty of this
AI agent is that you set it up once and
it runs forever, which makes you much
less likely to fall for any fishing
scams compared to the average person.
All right, so let's jump into NA10 and
let's look at it. Now, if you don't know
what NA10 is, it's basically the
simplest way to build AI agents. In
fact, it's so simple that you don't have
to be a programmer at all to start
building. It's literally drag and drop.
So, let me explain this AI agent. On the
first glance, it might look complicated,
but it's much simpler than you think.
And we're going to start by running the
full workflow. So, let me click on
execute workflow. It's going to fetch an
email and then run it through the whole
agent analyzing it through multiple
different sites. So, let's break it
down. Gmail trigger, pretty
self-explanatory. It runs on your email
and it checks your inbox every minute to
see if there's any new emails that you
received that haven't been checked yet.
Then, it sends the email content into
this node which splits it into batches
in case there is multiple URLs. Now, it
seems like the AI agent has finished
running. So, in a second, I'll show you
the results of it. But first, let me
explain this code block because this is
where a lot of people get intimidated.
And it's actually very simple. We just
use regular expressions with a short
Python script, which by the way, I got
Claude to write. So you don't have to do
any programming yourself. All you need
to do is ask like, write me a simple
script that parses raw body of a Gmail
and extracts URLs using regular
expressions. And even if you don't know
regular expressions or what they are,
you can just say, write me a simple
Python script to do X, right? Just
describe what you want. Claude just
released Sonet 4.5 and this model is
really really good. It will figure it
out. So as you can see Claude gave me a
simple script. So what you would do is
copy it. Boom. And just paste it inside
of the code block node to kind of clean
it up, right? That's because then we
have a if else note. This figures out if
there is a URL or not because not every
email that you receive is going to have
some link, right? Most emails probably
don't have any links. But if there is a
link, you want to make sure that we run
it through VUS total. So then here we
have a HTTP node which sends a simple
post request to the API of V total but
at the same time we also check URL scan.
So URL scan is a similar service where
it checks the contents of the URL for
any malicious files or redirects or
stuff like that. Right? So even if half
of this automation fails, you still get
protected. So we hit both of these at
the same time. Now URL scan is a bit um
flaky sometimes it fails. So that's why
we have this error protection and it
also needs a 60-second delay, right? So
we have this weight node but then we get
the reports from both of these and we
merge them using this node combine and
then we clean the data once again. This
time we use JavaScript. It doesn't
really matter to be honest like you can
just py for JavaScript. Again I got chbd
or claw to write this super simple. And
the reason we need to clean that up is
because here we have the AI agent. This
is the brain of the whole automation. So
let's look at how the AI agent works.
Right? So first of all it has AI model.
We're using GPD 4 mini. This is the
go-to uh cheap model for AI agents.
Honestly, if you want a really powerful
model, right now the set just released,
so enthropic, you can change that and
you can instead use enthropic models
with the new cloth 4.5 set, which by the
way, if you want me to make a video on
that, make sure to subscribe and comment
below. Sonet 4.5 and I'll make a video
because this model is insane. Anyways,
for cost effective reasons, GBD4 mini is
a great choice. So, let's look at the
system prompt because this is what
matters. To be honest, this system
probably is a bit advanced, so feel free
to pause and take it. But basically,
what we do is we pass it all of the
results from V total, from URL scan. We
give it the raw URL, we give it the raw
email data and anything else the AI
agent might need to make a decision on
whether this is a safe email, whether
it's, you know, on the edge or whether
it is malicious. And this really is the
power of AI agents because normally you
would have to do, you know, some
parsing, some regular expressions to
figure out if there's some like keywords
or some blacklist. But the AI agent can
make the decision for you, right? He can
take the inputs and figure out is this a
suspicious email? Is this catchy? And if
so, it uses this tool that send you a
Gmail message. Now, if you want
something else, you can do Telegram. It
can DM you on Telegram. You can do
Discord. You can do WhatsApp. However
you want AI agent to contact you. Now,
this N10 automation is already very
useful, but if you think this is
impressive, just wait until you see the
other two AI agents. Oh, and by the way,
as I promised, here's what it looks like
when the AI agent sends you the email.
As you can see, this one was marked as
safe. Now, the biggest problem with AI
agents is that they are only useful if
they actually run 24/7. Because if you
build an AI agent and it never runs,
it's pointless. Now, the easiest way to
make your AI agents run 24/7 is by
hosting your own virtual private server.
And believe it or not, this is much
simpler than you think. The easiest way
to do this is with Hostinger, which is
what I use for all of my AI agents. And
the reason is they have optimized their
VPS for NA10. Plus, the setup is super
simple. Let me show you. So, first off,
to visit the Hostinger site, click the
link below the video and then click on
choose your plan. Now, Hostinger offers
many different VPS plans, but I think
the KVN2 one is perfect for most of you,
and it's also the one me and my team use
internally. So, click on choose plan,
and this will redirect you to the
checkout. here. Select the period. I
recommend going 24 months because when
you build your agents, you want them to
be running forever. Plus, you get a
really, really solid deal when you go
with the 24-month plan. You even get a
free domain for a year as a bonus. And
since Hostinger was kind enough to
sponsor this video, if you click on have
coupon code and type in David, you will
get another 10% off of your plan. Next,
we need to select the location of our
server. So, just select whatever is the
closest to you. I'm going to go with
France. And then we need to select the
operating system. Now, since we're
building AI agents in NA10, obviously
we're going to select NA10 right here.
And then what remains is finishing the
checkout. So, click on continue. Next,
we need to create an account. And this
takes 20 seconds. Super simple. Now,
after you sign up, you get redirected to
the billing page where you fill out your
name and your billing details and
complete the purchase of your VPS. And
once you complete the purchase, you will
find your VPS server right here in your
hosting panel. And you can see it's
already running. So, click on manage.
And here you can see all the details
about your virtual private server, CPU
usage, memory, outgoing traffic. This is
literally enough to run hundreds of AI
agents. But what we need to do is we
need to click on manage app. And this
will bring you to your NA10 server when
you can manage all of your AI agents. So
if you're serious about building AI
agents, make sure to check out
Hostinger. Use the link below the video.
It really is the simplest way to host
your AI agents. Now, the third lesson in
cyber security is using multiple emails.
A lot of people have a single email for
everything and this is terrible. What
you need to do is you need to separate
your sensitive accounts like your
banking, your finance, your login from
the email you use for public
communication. For example, you could
have email for applying for jobs,
sending code emails, email for banking
apps, sensitive work, and so on. Now,
this is already a pretty advanced setup,
but just having two different email
addresses, right? one for all the public
facing stuff that other people have and
another that's like a series of random
characters that only you know that
already hits the 80 to 20. The next
lesson is updating your software. Now
most conspiracy theories turn out to be
true. But one that is not true is that
companies are scheming to slow your
software down and that you shouldn't
upgrade. This is very dumb because most
software upgrades also include some
security fixes. So when there is an
actual breach or some hack, software
companies work day and night to fix it
as soon as possible. And by having the
latest update, you protect yourself
against most of the known exploits. But
if all of your software is running old
versions, you are exposing yourself to
unnecessary risk. And the solution can
be as simple as enabling auto update on
most of your sensitive apps. The next
essential cyber security tip you need to
know is email breach alerts. Now, what
even are email breach alerts? They're
automatic warnings when something
sketchy happens with your email. Now,
basically, every month there is a
massive email breach of millions of
accounts and you won't be notified when
your email is included in these
breaches. Now, of course, there are many
issues if someone gains access to your
email as a result of your email being
included in a breach, right? They can
access your banking information. They
can change your passwords. They can
email people on your behalf. It is a
mess. And this can be much harder to
detect because what if the attackers set
up auto forwarding rules that you don't
notice on your email? It might take you
weeks or months before you notice. Now,
luckily, there's a way to prevent it and
that's by building an AI agent that
monitors your main emails to see if they
have been included in one of the recent
breaches. And to do that, we're going to
use the famous website, have I been
pawned? This is a popular breach
notification service that will notify
you if your email has been compromised.
Now, if you think, David, you know, I
keep my email safe. I I have multiple
passwords. My password is strong, right?
There's 15 billion accounts that have
been compromised. So, check your emails.
You'll be surprised. Now, what happens
when you underestimate this threat is
that you can lose a lot of money. And
this happens even to big companies.
There was a Canadian university that
lost $10 million. The part supplier to
Toyota lost 37 million through a simple
email scam. Now, luckily, you can
prevent this with this simple AI agent.
So, as you can see, there's a lot less
modules or nodes here than the first
one, but it's even more powerful. So, we
have a schedule trigger. This runs every
single day at 9:00 a.m. You can change
this to run once a week if you want, but
I think daily is good. And then it gets
a list of your emails for Google Sheets,
right? So again I recommend you having
multiple emails minimum two minimum one
for secure stuff and one public facing
email but ideally you have a lot more
than two emails and you can keep them
securely in a single Google sheet which
then we check each of them through have
I been pawned. So again HTTP request to
the API of this website with your emails
being appended in a variable at the end
of the URL. This means that we are
regularly running all of your emails
through have I been pawned. Something
that most people never do or they do it
like once a year. If you set this up, it
checks it daily. So this is what I mean
that it's going to take your cyber
security to the next level. And again,
the report goes to an AI agent which can
decide whether something has been
compromised in which case it will decide
to notify you and if not all is good.
You can sleep well. But as you can see
it doesn't take a lot. This is like what
six nodes total and it's a very powerful
NA10 automation that you have to build
once and it works forever. This is the
beauty of AI agents. The next lesson is
kind of obvious but password sharing is
bad almost in all cases. Now it's one
thing sharing your Netflix with your
friends. It's another thing giving your
phone code to your wife to your
girlfriend. Those are much worse
practices, right? And it's not because
your girlfriend works for MSAD. It's
because the more people have access to
your accounts, the higher the attack
vector, right? All it takes is one
person to click a fishing link. And if
there's five people who can access your
email, it doesn't make your email five
times less secure. It's more like 25
times less secure. So even though it's
obvious, it doesn't hurt to remind
ourselves that the less password sharing
you do, the less likely it is that your
password gets leaked. The next lesson is
uninstalling apps. That's right. Even a
simple thing like this can reduce your
exposure to these exploits and breaches.
I mean, if there's an app on your phone
or your computer that you haven't used
for three plus months, just uninstall
it. Okay? There's no reason to have so
many apps. You also save storage, but
most importantly, you reduce the attack
surface of something being compromised,
right? If you have 100 pieces of
software on your machine, it's much more
likely that one of them has some exploit
than if you only have the 20 apps that
you actually use. So, just try to keep
your devices as clean as possible and
get into habit of uninstalling an app
for each new app that you install. Real
quick, if you're finding this video
valuable, please make sure to subscribe.
It takes 2 seconds, it's completely
free, and it tells me that you want to
see more videos like this one. Thank
you. Now, the next lesson is a bit more
advanced, and that is auditing your
websites, especially if you're a VIP
coder. Okay? So, if you used AI to build
any software in the last two years, pay
attention. Now again, I build an AI
agent that will do this for us, but it
is very likely that your website is
either not secure, it's leaking more
information, it has some authentication
oversight or some other security issue.
You don't want hackers or bad actors to
find that out. You want yourself to find
it out and to fix it. So I call this AI
agent the website security auditor. And
basically what it does is that it
regularly tries to pentest. Pentesting
means penetration testing, which means
checking your website for any
vulnerabilities. And this is especially
important if you are building a startup,
right? Because not only can they hack
your own accounts, they can get customer
data as well. And that really is the
worst case scenario. You know, just last
month there was the T app which got a
massive breach because it was sloppy and
it left an exposed Firebase bucket that
was publicly accessible to anyone with
that URL. Now, if that person had this
AI agent that I'm about to show you,
they probably wouldn't have ruined their
whole startup. So here is what the agent
looks like. The trigger is a landing
page URL, right? So obviously you're
going to put your own website or if
you're doing this for a client, maybe
you can put his website. So then we take
the URL and we scrape the contents of
the website which we route into two
different paths with two different AI
agents on each path. So on the top one
we have a code node which extracts the
headers and sends those into our
security AI agent. And this one just
does a very basic analysis of any
leaking metadata or issues with your
headers specifically. Now the agent at
the bottom is running a more powerful
model like GBD5. You can also change it
for you know sonet 4.5 to have one open
AI and one entropic to have even more
exposure. But basically these two agents
look at your website at the structure of
your landing page and your login page
and look for potential ways that a
hacker might attack your website. Now to
be perfectly clear, if someone is a
professional hacker and wants to hack
you, you probably stand no chance,
right? Because those are genius
programmers. So the best thing is do not
piss off any hackers. But this is just
another protection that if you build a
VIP coded site, having this N10
automation run through it is going to
decrease the likelihood of you having
any obvious exploits on your landing
page. All right, so let's continue. We
have the merge node. Again, we merge the
outputs of these two agents into a
single result. We then aggregate the
results. We run them through two
different code nodes. This one is
processing and parsing and the second
one converts it to HTML. That way we can
then send it through an email. Again,
feel free to use something else. Slack,
Discord, Telegram, whatever you want to
be notified on, right? It doesn't have
to be Gmail. The reason I added Gmail is
because everybody has a Gmail, let's be
honest. So yeah, this AI agent pretty
simple even though it might look
intimidating, but if you've built a AI
coded website over the last 2 years,
please run it through an NAN automation
like this one so you don't have any
sloppy security issues. Next up, if you
don't already use a VPN, you probably
should, right? First of all, if you live
in the UK, the government just wants to
track you completely, so you need a VPN
just for that. Second of all, if you're
using, you know, like airport Wi-Fi or
McDonald's Wi-Fi, having another layer
of security never hurts. So, what a VPN
does is that it hides your IP address
from the sites and the apps that you
use, which makes it harder for attackers
or governments to track where you are,
where you're coming from, stuff like
that. Now, a pro tip when it comes to
VPNs, just please check who owns the
company of your VPN because let's just
say a lot of these VPN companies are
owned by people like the Versell CEO and
his friends. If you know, you know.
Anyways, the last bonus tip is something
that even Zach himself, which is a, you
know, professional programmer and a
multi-billionaire uses, and that is
taping your ports. Right? So if you work
in an office especially, a lot of
monitors, a lot of displays have like
USB ports behind them. You can go to the
next level and do that even for a
laptop, right? And the reason why you
should do this is that you never know if
someone inserts like a USB stick into
like a hidden port in your PC in the
back. It can take you months if not
years to notice. Another thing is having
this camera cover, right? This is
something you can buy on Amazon for like
$2 or $3, and it's a great thing to have
for extra peace of mind. It allows you
to still have your camera on your
laptop. So, it's much better than just
taping it. But if you aren't on a video
call, just slide it over and it's
covered. And obviously, physical
protection is better than just hoping
the software is good. So, those were 10
cyber security fundamentals. Again,
thank you Hostinger for sponsoring this
video. If you use NA10, which you
absolutely should, make sure to switch
over to Hostinger. It's the most
affordable solution. It's super easy to
set up and with a single VPS, especially
if you go with the KVM2 plan, you can
run like thousands of AI agents without
hitting any limits. There's no limits on
workflows, no limits on executions. You
have your own VPS. You can see all the
stats. This is why I use Hostinger for
all of my AI agents, and this is why you
should use Hostinger as well. So again,
use my link below the video and use the
code David for another 10% off. With
that being said, thank you guys for
watching and have a nice rest of your
day. See you.